<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Al-Ameen Caps – Islamic Headwear</title>
    <link>https://alameencaps.com/shop</link>
    <description>Handcrafted kufi, fez, taj, turban and Islamic headwear. Cape Town, South Africa.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 12:58:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-za</language>
  <item>
    <g:id>collection-1</g:id>
    <g:title>Na&apos;lain Cap premium quality</g:title>
    <g:description>Na&apos;lain Premium Cap — Signature Collection  Crafted for those who carry tradition with quiet confidence, the Na&apos;lain Premium Cap blends timeless Islamic heritage with refined modern craftsmanship.  Inspired by sacred geometry and classical artistry, the elegant embroidered motif crowns a cap designed for comfort, dignity, and everyday wear — whether for Jumu&apos;ah, special gatherings, or daily devotion.  Each piece reflects meticulous attention to detail: clean stitching, breathable fabric, and a structured form that maintains its shape while offering all-day comfort.  Why customers love it • Premium woven construction for durability and comfort • Elegant embroidered design inspired by sacred tradition • Lightweight and breathable for daily wear • Maintains shape and structure over time • Suitable for masjid, events, and everyday use  More than just headwear, the Na&apos;lain Premium Cap is a statement of identity — honoring heritage while embracing modern style.  Wear it with dignity. Carry tradition with pride.  🛒 Limited stock available — add yours to cart today.</g:description>
    <g:link>https://alameencaps.com/product/collection-1</g:link>
    <g:image_link>https://alameencaps.com/collection/nalain-cap.png</g:image_link>
    <g:availability>in_stock</g:availability>
    <g:price>145.00 ZAR</g:price>
    <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    <g:brand>Al-Ameen Caps</g:brand>
    <g:google_product_category>166</g:google_product_category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <g:id>collection-2</g:id>
    <g:title>Afgani Star Cap Premium quality</g:title>
    <g:description>Afgani Star Cap — Premium Collection  Designed for men who value heritage and refined simplicity, the Afgani Star Cap brings together classic Afghan-inspired style with modern craftsmanship.  Its structured form, soft premium fabric, and clean finish make it ideal for Jumu&apos;ah, gatherings, or daily wear. Available in a range of elegant tones, each cap complements both traditional and modern attire.  Built for comfort and durability, the Afgani Star Cap maintains its shape while remaining breathable for all-day use.  Why customers choose it • Premium fabric with soft, durable finish • Classic structured Afghan design • Comfortable and breathable for daily wear • Maintains shape over time • Suitable for masjid, events, and everyday style  More than headwear, the Afgani Star Cap reflects dignity, heritage, and confident style.  🛒 Limited stock available — add yours to cart today.</g:description>
    <g:link>https://alameencaps.com/product/collection-2</g:link>
    <g:image_link>https://alameencaps.com/collection/afgani-star-cap.png</g:image_link>
    <g:availability>in_stock</g:availability>
    <g:price>135.00 ZAR</g:price>
    <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    <g:brand>Al-Ameen Caps</g:brand>
    <g:google_product_category>166</g:google_product_category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <g:id>collection-3</g:id>
    <g:title>Saqib shami cap Premium</g:title>
    <g:description>Saqib Shami Cap — Royal Premium Collection  The Saqib Shami Cap is crafted for those who appreciate regal tradition and commanding elegance. Inspired by classical Shami ceremonial headwear, this cap carries a presence that instantly elevates formal attire.  Its layered construction, intricate weaving, and rich crown detailing reflect royal heritage, making it a perfect choice for weddings, special gatherings, Eid occasions, and distinguished events.  Designed with premium materials, it delivers both comfort and structure, ensuring the cap maintains its dignified shape while remaining comfortable for long wear.  Why customers choose it • Royal ceremonial design with bold visual presence • Rich crown detailing that stands out in formal settings • Structured layered build for a distinguished profile • Ideal for weddings, Eid, and special occasions • A statement piece for those who value tradition and prestige  More than headwear, the Saqib Shami Cap is a symbol of heritage, honor, and royal style.  🛒 Limited stock available — secure yours today.</g:description>
    <g:link>https://alameencaps.com/product/collection-3</g:link>
    <g:image_link>https://alameencaps.com/collection/saqib-shami-cap.png</g:image_link>
    <g:availability>in_stock</g:availability>
    <g:price>660.00 ZAR</g:price>
    <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    <g:brand>Al-Ameen Caps</g:brand>
    <g:google_product_category>166</g:google_product_category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <g:id>collection-4</g:id>
    <g:title>Azhari hard Caps</g:title>
    <g:description>Azhari Hard Cap — Scholar&apos;s Collection  The Azhari Hard Cap reflects the timeless scholarly tradition associated with the great centers of Islamic learning. Recognized for its clean structure and dignified form, this cap is designed for those who carry knowledge, leadership, and tradition with pride.  Its firm construction maintains a sharp, elegant profile, making it ideal for imams, students of knowledge, and formal religious gatherings. The classic color contrast further enhances its distinguished appearance.  Crafted for durability and comfort, the cap retains its shape while remaining suitable for extended wear.  Why customers choose it • Iconic Azhari-inspired scholarly design • Firm structured build for a dignified appearance • Ideal for imams, scholars, and formal religious occasions • Durable construction that keeps its shape • A respected symbol of knowledge and tradition  A cap that represents scholarship, dignity, and timeless Islamic heritage.  🛒 Limited stock available — add yours to cart today.</g:description>
    <g:link>https://alameencaps.com/product/collection-4</g:link>
    <g:image_link>https://alameencaps.com/collection/azhari-hard-cap.png</g:image_link>
    <g:availability>preorder</g:availability>
    <g:price>600.00 ZAR</g:price>
    <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    <g:brand>Al-Ameen Caps</g:brand>
    <g:google_product_category>166</g:google_product_category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <g:id>collection-5</g:id>
    <g:title>Naqshbandi Taj</g:title>
    <g:description>Naqshbandi Taj — Spiritual Heritage Collection  The Naqshbandi Taj represents spiritual refinement and timeless Sufi tradition. Designed with elegance and simplicity, this Taj reflects humility, discipline, and inner dignity — values long associated with the Naqshbandi spiritual path.  Its rounded, layered structure and subtle detailing create a calm yet distinguished presence, making it ideal for spiritual gatherings, dhikr assemblies, and special religious occasions.  Crafted for comfort and graceful appearance, the Taj maintains its form while offering light, breathable wear for extended use.  Why customers choose it • Traditional Taj design inspired by Sufi heritage • Elegant layered form symbolizing spiritual discipline • Ideal for gatherings, dhikr, and sacred occasions • Lightweight and comfortable for extended wear • A symbol of humility and spiritual identity  More than headwear, the Naqshbandi Taj represents tradition, devotion, and inner refinement.  🛒 Limited pieces available — secure yours today.</g:description>
    <g:link>https://alameencaps.com/product/collection-5</g:link>
    <g:image_link>https://alameencaps.com/collection/naqshbandi-taj.png</g:image_link>
    <g:availability>in_stock</g:availability>
    <g:price>990.00 ZAR</g:price>
    <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    <g:brand>Al-Ameen Caps</g:brand>
    <g:google_product_category>166</g:google_product_category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <g:id>collection-6</g:id>
    <g:title>Luxury Arabic Rumal</g:title>
    <g:description>Luxury Arabic Rumal — Classic Desert Collection  The Luxury Arabic Rumal blends timeless Middle Eastern tradition with modern versatility. Known for its distinctive woven patterns and flowing tassel finish, the rumal has long been worn as both a practical and stylish garment across the Arab world.  Crafted from soft, breathable fabric, it provides comfort in warm and cool conditions while adding character to both traditional and contemporary outfits. Whether worn around the neck, over the shoulders, or styled as headwear, it offers effortless elegance.  Why customers choose it • Authentic Arabic woven pattern with premium finish • Soft, breathable fabric suitable for all seasons • Versatile styling for daily wear or travel • Adds character to both traditional and modern attire • Durable weave with elegant tassel detailing  A timeless accessory that combines function, culture, and refined style.  🛒 Limited stock available — add yours to cart today.</g:description>
    <g:link>https://alameencaps.com/product/collection-6</g:link>
    <g:image_link>https://alameencaps.com/collection/luxury-arabic-rumal.png</g:image_link>
    <g:availability>in_stock</g:availability>
    <g:price>250.00 ZAR</g:price>
    <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    <g:brand>Al-Ameen Caps</g:brand>
    <g:google_product_category>166</g:google_product_category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <g:id>collection-7</g:id>
    <g:title>Special Ashrafi taj</g:title>
    <g:description>The Special Ashrafi Taj is a rare prestige piece, crafted for those who appreciate deep spiritual heritage and ceremonial elegance. Handwoven by master craftsmen from the Ansaar family, descendants connected to the noble household of Ahlul Bayt (SAW), this Taj carries both artistry and legacy.  Its rich layered wrapping and elevated crown design create a commanding yet graceful presence, traditionally worn during sacred gatherings, Mawlid, spiritual assemblies, and distinguished occasions.  Each piece reflects meticulous handcraftsmanship, resulting in a Taj that embodies respect, devotion, and noble tradition.  Why collectors and devotees choose it • Handwoven by master craftsmen of the Ansaar lineage • Ceremonial Ashrafi design reserved for special occasions • Rich layered construction symbolizing honor and tradition • Prestige piece rarely available in the open market • Ideal for Mawlid, spiritual gatherings, and ceremonial wear  More than headwear, the Special Ashrafi Taj represents lineage, craftsmanship, and spiritual prestige.  🛒 Only one piece available — a rare addition for those who value heritage and distinction.</g:description>
    <g:link>https://alameencaps.com/product/collection-7</g:link>
    <g:image_link>https://alameencaps.com/collection/special-ashrafi-taj.png</g:image_link>
    <g:availability>in_stock</g:availability>
    <g:price>1600.00 ZAR</g:price>
    <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    <g:brand>Al-Ameen Caps</g:brand>
    <g:google_product_category>166</g:google_product_category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <g:id>collection-8</g:id>
    <g:title>Geuvara Military Cap (Afgan style)</g:title>
    <g:description>Guevara Military Cap — Cuban-Afghan Hybrid Collection  Inspired by the iconic revolutionary style associated with Che Guevara and blended with traditional Afghan Pakol craftsmanship, the Guevara Military Cap delivers a bold Cuban-Afghan hybrid look. Designed for men who appreciate heritage with a strong, modern edge, this cap makes a confident statement wherever it&apos;s worn.  Crafted from soft yet durable fabric, the structured military profile meets the comfort of the classic rolled Pakol form, while the metal star insignia reinforces its rugged, commanding appeal. Perfect for casual wear, travel, and outdoor styling.  Why customers choose it • Unique Cuban-Afghan hybrid military design • Signature star insignia for a bold visual statement • Soft, warm fabric suited for cooler conditions • Comfortable rolled construction for daily wear • Ideal for casual, travel, and street styling  A cap that merges tradition, resilience, and unmistakable character.  🛒 Limited stock available — add yours to cart today.</g:description>
    <g:link>https://alameencaps.com/product/collection-8</g:link>
    <g:image_link>https://alameencaps.com/collection/geuvara-military-cap.png</g:image_link>
    <g:availability>in_stock</g:availability>
    <g:price>250.00 ZAR</g:price>
    <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    <g:brand>Al-Ameen Caps</g:brand>
    <g:google_product_category>166</g:google_product_category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <g:id>collection-9</g:id>
    <g:title>Al Hassan perfumes without alcohol</g:title>
    <g:description>Al Hassan Perfumes — Alcohol-Free Collection  Discover the richness of Arabian fragrance with Al Hassan Alcohol-Free Perfumes, crafted for long-lasting scent and everyday elegance. Perfect for daily wear, prayer, and special occasions.  Available Scents  White Oudh – Smooth, refined oud with a soft woody warmth, ideal for daily elegance.  Ameer Al Oudh – Deep, rich, and powerful oud with warm amber tones, perfect for evening and special occasions.  Baccarat Rouge Style – Modern, sweet, and musky notes for a bold, contemporary signature scent.  Why customers choose it • Alcohol-free and skin-friendly • Long-lasting fragrance • Perfect for daily and occasion wear • Elegant, gift-ready presentation  🛒 Choose your signature scent today.</g:description>
    <g:link>https://alameencaps.com/product/collection-9</g:link>
    <g:image_link>https://alameencaps.com/collection/al-hassan-perfume.png</g:image_link>
    <g:availability>in_stock</g:availability>
    <g:price>135.00 ZAR</g:price>
    <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    <g:brand>Al-Ameen Caps</g:brand>
    <g:google_product_category>166</g:google_product_category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <g:id>collection-10</g:id>
    <g:title>Mufti Cap premium quality</g:title>
    <g:description>Mufti Cap — Premium Collection  The Mufti Premium Cap combines classic scholarship style with refined embroidery, creating a cap suited for both formal and everyday wear. Designed with rich detailing and premium stitching, it offers a dignified look while remaining comfortable throughout the day.  Available in striking red, black, and gold variations, each cap adds elegance to traditional attire while maintaining a clean, structured profile.  Why customers choose it • Detailed embroidery with premium finish • Comfortable and breathable for daily wear • Structured design that keeps its shape • Ideal for masjid, gatherings, and formal occasions • Available in rich, elegant color options  🛒 Limited stock available — add yours to cart today.</g:description>
    <g:link>https://alameencaps.com/product/collection-10</g:link>
    <g:image_link>https://alameencaps.com/collection/mufti-cap.png</g:image_link>
    <g:availability>in_stock</g:availability>
    <g:price>200.00 ZAR</g:price>
    <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    <g:brand>Al-Ameen Caps</g:brand>
    <g:google_product_category>166</g:google_product_category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <g:id>collection-11</g:id>
    <g:title>Ertugral Winter cap</g:title>
    <g:description>Ertugral Winter Cap — Qadiriyah Collection  Inspired by the legendary Ertugral style and linked to Qadiriyah heritage aesthetics, this Ertugral Winter Cap combines rugged tradition with winter-ready craftsmanship. Its conical leather structure and warm faux-fur brim create a bold, commanding look while offering excellent cold-weather protection.  Designed for outdoor wear and winter gatherings, the cap blends historical warrior style with modern comfort, making it both practical and distinctive.  Why customers choose it • Ertugral-inspired winter warrior design • Durable leather finish with warm fur-lined brim • Provides warmth and comfort in cold conditions • Distinctive emblem detailing for added character • Ideal for winter wear and outdoor styling  A winter cap that carries strength, heritage, and unmistakable presence.  🛒 Limited stock available — add yours to cart today.</g:description>
    <g:link>https://alameencaps.com/product/collection-11</g:link>
    <g:image_link>https://alameencaps.com/collection/ertugral-winter-cap.png</g:image_link>
    <g:availability>out_of_stock</g:availability>
    <g:price>650.00 ZAR</g:price>
    <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    <g:brand>Al-Ameen Caps</g:brand>
    <g:google_product_category>166</g:google_product_category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <g:id>collection-12</g:id>
    <g:title>Royal Ottoman Fez</g:title>
    <g:description>Royal Ottoman Fez — Heritage Collection  The Royal Ottoman Fez is a timeless symbol of dignity and classical Ottoman elegance. Crafted from premium velvet with its signature black tassel, this fez delivers a refined presence suited for ceremonial wear, formal gatherings, and cultural occasions.  Made with exceptional craftsmanship and durable construction, this is among the finest quality fez caps available — designed to maintain its shape and beauty for years, often lasting a lifetime with proper care.  Why customers choose it • Premium velvet finish with classic Ottoman design • Durable, structured build for long-term use • Elegant tassel detail completing the traditional look • Ideal for ceremonies, events, and cultural attire • A timeless piece that never goes out of style  A fez that carries history, elegance, and lasting quality.</g:description>
    <g:link>https://alameencaps.com/product/collection-12</g:link>
    <g:image_link>https://alameencaps.com/collection/royal-ottoman-fez.png</g:image_link>
    <g:availability>in_stock</g:availability>
    <g:price>550.00 ZAR</g:price>
    <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    <g:brand>Al-Ameen Caps</g:brand>
    <g:google_product_category>166</g:google_product_category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <g:id>collection-13</g:id>
    <g:title>Emerald Sultan Crown</g:title>
    <g:description>A symbol of dignity and refined tradition. The Emerald Sultan Crown features a deep emerald-green velvet top, detailed with elegant white radial stitching and a classic central button finish. The crisp white structured base creates a powerful contrast, giving the piece a royal and commanding presence.  Designed for men who carry themselves with confidence and honour, this cap is perfect for Jumu&apos;ah, Eid, special gatherings, or formal occasions. A timeless statement of faith, prestige, and craftsmanship.</g:description>
    <g:link>https://alameencaps.com/product/collection-13</g:link>
    <g:image_link>https://alameencaps.com/collection/emerald-sultan-crown.png</g:image_link>
    <g:availability>in_stock</g:availability>
    <g:price>1200.00 ZAR</g:price>
    <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    <g:brand>Al-Ameen Caps</g:brand>
    <g:google_product_category>166</g:google_product_category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <g:id>collection-14</g:id>
    <g:title>Turkish Naqshbandi Taj</g:title>
    <g:description>A powerful expression of spiritual lineage and refined tradition. The Turkish Naqshbandi Taj is meticulously wrapped with precision-folded layers, forming a structured and commanding silhouette rooted in classical Turkish and Naqshbandi heritage.  Available in timeless shades of deep black, pure white, and rich emerald green, each Taj reflects balance, discipline, and inner strength. The clean, symmetrical wrapping represents order and spiritual focus, while the firm construction ensures lasting shape and dignified comfort throughout the day.  Ideal for scholars, seekers, and men of presence, this Taj is suited for Jumu&apos;ah, Eid, nikah ceremonies, dhikr gatherings, and formal spiritual occasions. It is not merely worn—it is carried with intention.  A mark of humility and authority. A symbol of the Naqshbandi path.</g:description>
    <g:link>https://alameencaps.com/product/collection-14</g:link>
    <g:image_link>https://alameencaps.com/collection/turkish-naqshbandi-taj.png</g:image_link>
    <g:availability>in_stock</g:availability>
    <g:price>950.00 ZAR</g:price>
    <g:condition>new</g:condition>
    <g:brand>Al-Ameen Caps</g:brand>
    <g:google_product_category>166</g:google_product_category>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>